<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">App2</string>
    <string name="mode">mode</string>
    <string name="notes">Notes</string>
    <string name="save">save</string>
    <string name="dessertly">DESSERTLY</string>
    <string name="find_the_foodie_in_you">Find the foodie in you</string>
    <string name="start_cooking">Start Cooking</string>
    <string name="capture">capture</string>
    <string name="delete">delete</string>
    <string name="todo" tools:ignore="DuplicateDefinition">TODO</string>
    <string name="add_note" tools:ignore="DuplicateDefinition">Add a note…</string>
    <string name="clear">clear</string>
    <string name="capture_result">Capture Result</string>
    <string name="complete">complete</string>

    <!--CHOCOLATE MOLTEN CAKES-->
    <string name="molten">Chocolate Molten Cakes</string>
    <string name="molten_desc">Bake an impressive dinner party dessert with minimum fuss – these
        chocolate puddings, also known as chocolate fondant or lava cake, have a lovely gooey
        centre.</string>
    <string name="molten_text"><b>Ingredients</b>\n
        • 100g butter, plus extra to grease\n
        • 100g dark chocolate, chopped\n
        • 150g light brown soft sugar\n
        • 3 large eggs\n
        • ½ tsp vanilla extract\n
        • 50g plain flour\n
        • single cream, to serve\n\n

        <b>Method</b>\n
        <i>Step 1</i>\nHeat oven to 200C/180C fan/gas 6. Butter 6 dariole moulds or basins well and
        place on a baking tray.\n\n
        <i>Step 2</i>\nPut 100g butter and 100g chopped dark chocolate in a heatproof bowl and set
        over a pan of hot water (or alternatively put in the microwave and melt in 30 second bursts
        on a low setting) and stir until smooth. Set aside to cool slightly for 15 minutes.\n\n
        <i>Step 3</i>\nUsing an electric hand whisk, mix in 150g light brown soft sugar, then 3 large
        eggs, one at a time, followed by ½ tsp vanilla extract and finally 50g plain flour. Divide
        the mixture among the darioles or basins.\n\n
        <i>Step 4</i>\nYou can now either put the mixture in the fridge, or freezer until you\'re ready
        to bake them. Can be cooked straight from frozen for 16 minutes, or bake now for 10-12
        minutes until the tops are firm to the touch but the middles still feel squidgy.\n\n
        <i>Step 5</i>\nCarefully run a knife around the edge of each pudding, then turn out onto
        serving plates and serve with single cream.\n</string>

    <!--CHERRY & ALMOND FRANGIPANE GALETTE -->
    <string name="frangipane">Cherry &amp; Almond Frangipane Galette</string>
    <string name="frangipane_desc">Use spelt pastry for this free-form pie, as its nuttiness
        complements the frangipane. The combination of squishy baked cherries and juicy fresh
        ones is lovely.</string>
    <string name="frangipane_text"><b>Ingredients</b>\n
        • 400g cherries , pitted and halved\n
        • 1 tsp caster sugar\n
        • 1 tbsp lemon juice\n
        • 3 tbsp morello cherry conserve\n
        • 1 egg , beaten\n
        • 2 tbsp granulated sugar\n
        • clotted cream, to serve (optional)\n
        <b>For the pastry</b>\n
        • 200g white spelt flour\n
        • 1 tbsp caster sugar\n
        • 120g unsalted butter, chilled and cut into cubes\n
        <b>For the frangipane</b>\n
        • 100g whole, skin-on almonds, toasted\n
        • 15g unsalted butter\n
        • 1 tbsp spelt flour, plus extra for dusting\n
        • ½ tsp vanilla essence\n
        • 50g golden caster sugar\n
        • 1 egg\n\n

        <b>Method</b>\n
        <i>Step 1</i>\nHeat oven to 200C/180C fan/gas 6. Butter 6 dariole moulds or basins well and
        place on a baking tray.\n\n
        <i>Step 2</i>\nPut 100g butter and 100g chopped dark chocolate in a heatproof bowl and set
        over a pan of hot water (or alternatively put in the microwave and melt in 30 second bursts
        on a low setting) and stir until smooth. Set aside to cool slightly for 15 minutes.\n\n
        <i>Step 3</i>\nUsing an electric hand whisk, mix in 150g light brown soft sugar, then 3 large
        eggs, one at a time, followed by ½ tsp vanilla extract and finally 50g plain flour. Divide
        the mixture among the darioles or basins.\n\n
        <i>Step 4</i>\nYou can now either put the mixture in the fridge, or freezer until you\'re ready
        to bake them. Can be cooked straight from frozen for 16 minutes, or bake now for 10-12
        minutes until the tops are firm to the touch but the middles still feel squidgy.\n\n
        <i>Step 5</i>\nCarefully run a knife around the edge of each pudding, then turn out onto
        serving plates and serve with single cream.\n</string>


    <!--LEMON SPONGE CAKE-->
    <string name="sponge">Lemon Sponge Cake</string>
    <string name="sponge_desc">Top this citrussy sponge with lemon icing and candied peel. Greek
        yogurt creates a cake that\'s extra moist and tangy, for an irresistible teatime treat.</string>
    <string name="sponge_text"><b>Ingredients</b>\n
        • 175g unsalted butter, softened, plus extra for the tin\n
        • 175g golden caster sugar\n
        • 3 large eggs\n
        • 3 large unwaxed lemons, zested, plus 4-4 ½ tbsp juice\n
        • 250g self-raising flour\n
        • ½ tsp baking powder\n
        • 100g Greek yogurt\n
        • 400g icing sugar\n
        • Lemon zest or candied peel, to serve (optional)\n
        <b>For the candied peel</b>\n
         • 2 large lemons\n
         • 200g granulated sugar\n\n

        <b>Method</b>\n
        <i>Step 1</i>\nHeat oven to 170C/150C fan/gas 3. Butter a deep, loose-bottomed, 18cm cake
        tin and line the base with baking parchment. \n\n
        <i>Step 2</i>\nBeat the butter and caster sugar together with an electric whisk until fluffy
        and pale in colour. Crack the eggs in one at a time, beating well after each addition, then
        stir in the lemon zest. Fold in the flour, baking powder and ½ tsp salt, then fold in the
        yogurt.\n\n
        <i>Step 3</i>\nSpoon the mixture into the lined tin, smoothing the top with a spatula. Bake
        in the centre of the oven for 50-55 minutes, or until golden brown on top and firm to the
        touch. Cool in the tin for 10 minutes before turning out onto a wire rack to cool completely.
        Will keep in an airtight container for up to four days, or in the freezer for up to a month.\n\n
        <i>Step 4</i>\nWhen you\’re ready to decorate, sieve the icing sugar into a bowl and beat in
        enough of the lemon juice to create a thick icing. Set the cake on a serving plate or cake
        stand, then spoon over the icing, allowing it to drip down the sides a little. Top with the
        lemon zest or candied peel, if using (see below), and cut into generous wedges to serve.\n\n
        <i>Step 5</i>\nTo make candied lemon peel, peel large, wide strips from the lemons using a
        vegetable peeler. Remove any pith with a knife, then julienne the peel into very thin
        matchsticks. Tip the granulated sugar into a saucepan with 200ml water and set over a medium
        heat until the sugar has dissolved. Add the lemon peel and simmer gently for 15 minutes,
        then scoop the peel out using a slotted spoon and set on a piece of kitchen paper to cool.
        Use to decorate the top of your cake.\n</string>

    <!--LEMON SPONGE CAKE-->
    <!--LEMON SPONGE CAKE-->
    <!--LEMON SPONGE CAKE-->
    <!--LEMON SPONGE CAKE-->
    <!--LEMON SPONGE CAKE-->
    <!--LEMON SPONGE CAKE-->
    <!--LEMON SPONGE CAKE-->


</resources>